CURRICULUM VITAE

BEENA MATHEW

Mob No: 00971 552936387

Email: beenamoncy03@gmail.com

Visa status: Visiting Visa 14/3/2019 to 12/5/2019



OBJECTIVES:

A suitable position with an organization where I can utilize the best of my skills and abilities that fit to my education, skills and experience where I can provide comprehensive care for the welfare of my clients and society. Aims to achieve professional excellence intellectual abilities that gives scope to apply knowledge and skills in comprehensive nursing care that dynamically works toward the growth of organization.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

Exam passed	Institution	Board/University	Year
SSLC	NSS GHS, Perunna,	Board of Public Examinations	1997
	Changanassery	Kerala	
Pre Degree	St. John's College	M G University	1999
	Thiruvalla		

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION:

Level of Course	Institution	Period	Subject for Specialty
ANM	G.K. Hospital,	1999-2000	Nursing
(Nursing Assistant	Kavumbhagom		
Course)	Thiruvalla		
BLS Course	Academy of	15.03.2019	CPR and AED
(Basic Life support)	Global	to 03/2021	
	Education, India		

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Organization : Mangirish Surgical, Maternity & Children's Hospital,

Mumbai

Designation

: Assistant Nurse

Period

: 01.04.2001 to 06.05.2004

Department

: Medical Neotanal & Paediatric Ward

Organization

: Ministry of Social Affairs, Sulaibikhat, Kuwait

Designation

: Assistant Nurse

Period

: 28.09.2005 to 21.01.2010

Department

: Medical Department

Organization

: UTKARSH NURSING HOME, Mumbai

Designation

: Nurse

Period

: 05.03.2011 to 15.08.2016

Department

: Gynacology & Paediatric Ward

Organization

: S N Hospital, Kadapra, Kerala

Designation

: Nurse

Period

: 03.02.2017 to 10.03.2019

Department

: Medical Ward

STRENGTHS:

- Willing to work in shifts
- Self-starter with lots of enthusiasm and motivation.
- Ability to work in a team with excellent group dynamics.
- Ability to deal with people diplomatically
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.

AWARENESS:

- Very good Knowledge about various disease conditions & its Medical & Surgical management including collaborative nursing care.
- Very good Skills in providing Nursing care according to nursing processes.
- Good knowledge in handling emergency cases and trauma care.

SKILLS IN:

- Admission and Orientation of the patient.
- Assessing the needs of the patient.
- Plan nursing care as per the needs of patient.
- Provision of psychological support to the patient.
- Supporting the activities of daily living of the patient.
- Continuous monitoring by closed observation.
- Performing and assisting the life saving procedures such as CPR,
 Defibrillation, Pulse Oximetery, suctioning, etc.

PERSONAL PROFILE:

Name

BEENA MATHEW

Address

Palathinkal House

Ezhinjillam

Perumthuruti P.O. Thiruvalla-689107

India

Date of Birth

09.05.1980

Nationality

Indian

Marital Status

Married

Religion

Christian

Gender

Female

Languages known:

English, Arabic, Hindi, Malayalam

PASSPORT DETAILS:

Passport Number

J0700205

Date of issue

06.08.2010

Date of Expiry

05.08.2020

Place of Issue

Trivandrum